question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    }
]
